export const questions = [
	{
		question: "STD's can be passed from person to person through",
		options: [
			'Sexual contact',
			'Casual contact such as shaking hands',
			'Droplets such as coughing and sneezing',
			'All the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0, // Index of "Sexual contact"
	},
	{
		question:
			'Left untreated, which STD can cause deafness and death in its advanced stages?',
		options: ['Syphilis', 'Pubic Lice'],
		correctAnswer: 0, // Index of "Syphilis"
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of the following is a possible symptom of an STD?',
		options: [
			'Bumps, sores, or warts near the mouth, anus, vagina, penis',
			'Painful urination',
			'Painful sex',
			'All of the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3, // Index of "All of the above"
	},
	{
		question: 'Is a tumor associated with HIV-infected men.',
		options: [
			'Prostate carcinoma',
			'Liver cell carcinoma',
			'Osteosarcoma',
			"Kaposi's sarcoma",
		],
		correctAnswer: 3, // Index of "Kaposi's sarcoma"
	},
	{
		question: 'The bacterium Chlamydia trachomatis can cause:',
		options: [
			'Lymphogranuloma venereum (LGV) and orchitis',
			'Epididymitis and urethritis',
			'Chlamydia',
			'All of the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3, // Index of "All of the above"
	},
	{
		question: 'Which is the more unusual sexually transmitted infection?',
		options: ['Hepatitis B', 'Hepatitis C'],
		correctAnswer: 1, // Index of "Hepatitis C"
	},
	{
		question: 'Which is not a high-risk behavior?',
		options: [
			'Engaging in unprotected sexual activity',
			'Engaging in sexual activity with multiple partners',
			'Using alcohol and other drugs',
			'Abstaining from sexual activity',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3, // Index of "Abstaining from sexual activity"
	},
	{
		question: 'Getting a diagnoses and treatment is',
		options: [
			'Crucial for those infected with std’s',
			'Acting responsibly',
			'A healthy behavior',
			'All of the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3, // Index of "All of the above"
	},
	{
		question: 'During the course of HIV/AIDS, the infected person',
		options: [
			'Needs Less and less medication',
			'Gets stronger',
			'Should not hug anyone or shake hands',
			'Becomes vulnerable to opportunistic illnesses',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3, // Index of "Becomes vulnerable to opportunistic illnesses"
	},
	{
		question: 'It is difficult for antibodies to fight AIDS because:',
		options: [
			'HIV destroys white blood cells',
			'HIV is protected once it enters cells',
			'HIV weakens antibodies',
			'HIV mutates rapidly',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0, // Index of "HIV destroys white blood cells"
	},
	{
		question: "What is one reason STD's often go untreated",
		options: [
			"Most STD's are not serious",
			"Most STD's disappear on their own",
			"STD's may be asymptomatic",
			'There is no treatment or cure for most STD’s',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2, // Index of "STD's may be asymptomatic"
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which STD is sometimes difficult to cure because of drug-resistant strains',
		options: ['Genital HPV', 'Genital herpes', 'Gonorrhea', 'HIV'],
		correctAnswer: 2, // Index of "Gonorrhea"
	},
];
